From the beginning, we hated you, but also, we loved you from the beginning as well.
All we wanted was to become true friends with you, so we had to cross the wall.
A bear has crossed the Wall of Severance, our only line of defense.
Tragically, Sumika Izumino lost her life to that bear.
At this time, we have been unable to reach Kakyusha Akai and Konami Yurikawa, along with several other students from our school.
The fact is, we face our greatest crisis since the day of Severance.
That being said, a bear was shot last night that we believe to have been the invader, but we mustn't let our guard down.
It's important for you all to understand that the friends sitting next to you are the keys to your protection from here on out.
Never be alone for a moment, even on school grounds.
Ladies, you must protect each other. There is no other way.
Don't worry. I'll be the one to protect you.
Is something wrong?
I can't. I'm sorry.
But why not? What about yesterday?
Yesterday? I think you got the wrong idea.
Fine, be that way. It's your decision.
Damn it. She rejected me?
It's okay, though. It's okay.
The truth is, I kind of like this side of her.
The fun's only beginning, Kureha Tsubaki.
I'm gonna work you over real good, and then I'll eat you right on up.
Kureha Tsubaki.
How are you? Have you calmed down a bit?
Yes, ma'am.
Liar.
What?
You're not very good at it, though.
Raya was like that, too. Honest to a fault.
Raya? You mean my mom?
I do.
My, you remind me of that girl.
So much like your mother.
You mustn't suffer in silence, Kurea.
The more you try to hide the pain of losing a loved one, the more that pain will grow and become unbearable.
Unfortunately, I know this all too well myself.
Your mother? I lost Raya that day, too.
She was such a wonderful person.
She was my best friend.
And I'll never have another like her again. Never.
That's why I was so happy when you came to this school.
And when you decided to bring the flower bed back to life, it touched my heart.
I'm sure you didn't realize that place held special memories for Raya and me.
I hate bears.
Yes. So do I. After all, they took the ones we loved away from us.
There's another bear.
What?
There's another bear still out there.
But how? Wasn't the bear that attacked Sumika taken care of?
I thought your friend Mitsuko killed it.
She only killed one.
I saw them. Two bears.
I'm positive it's in this school. It has to be here.
That bear is somewhere close. Too close.
This school set up really is an excellent system for me.
All I have to do is hang out here for a while and wait for the right opportunity to present itself.
Hey Mitsuko. I want to volunteer. I was thinking since Konami's missing that maybe I could fill in for her today.
That's a great idea, Eriko. Class friendship naturally starts with individual responsibility. The leadership you're showing is awesome. Keep it up.
It is so nice.
Strong people are beautiful people.
Thank you, Mitsuko. We should be best friends.
There's my good girl. I can't waste any more time. I need to eat Kureha Tsubaki as soon as possible.
There's one more bear. I know it.
I'll never forgive the bears. I'll ruin them. Every one.
Rowl. Look at that girl. She's totally itching to shoot a bear.
This sucks. The only reason we came here tonight was to beat that sticky, icky Mitsuko Arizona to the dinner patch.
But we can't get close to her now.
So stupid. Who knew there'd be a rival bear at that school.
Punch, punch. Stop our disguises too. Punch, punch.
Delicious smell. Growl, growl.
Aw, jeez. You're so not even listening to me, Ginkgo.
Kureha Tsubaki must be the tastiest girl in the whole world, huh?
Pope Urban II's moving sermon at the Council of Claremont proved to be highly effective, summoning the armies of kings and nobility across most of Western Europe.
This effort formed the first army of Crusaders in 1096. Thus began a long series of wars in an attempt to regain the Holy Land from the Seljuk Turks.
Here. I think you forgot something.
Something.
All right, girls. Guess what will be on the test.
Please not this.
Are you kidding me? I'm not just talking to here myself.
Oh, Sumika. The time moves so slowly when you're not in class with me.
What this means is that the Crusades exposed the people of Western Europe to the drastically...
Will I start to forget everything now?
Forget that day? That moment?
Will I eventually forget love?
And be invisible, just like everyone else?
Your mother's flower bed?
Yeah. Mom told me that back when she was a student here, she built it with her best friend at the time.
Ah. So that's why you love it.
Of course. I want to fill it with lots of flowers again because I think she'd like it.
That's so sweet. You didn't give up on her love either, huh?
Never.
Your mother's precious garden. It's like your love for her.
Like my love how?
It's beautiful. And that's why I'm not gonna give up either, not on you. Not on my precious love. Our love.
Our love.
Oh, I want to fill it with lots of flowers again because I think she'd like it.
Ah, I want to fill it with lots of flowers again because I think she'd like it.
That's so sweet. You didn't give up on her love either, huh?
Never.
Your mother's precious garden. It's like your love for her.
Uh, like my love how?
It's beautiful. And that's why I'm not gonna give up either. Not on you. Not on my precious love. Our love.
Our love.
I won't forget.
I'll never forget.
Sumika, I swear I'll never give up on love.
Attention, ladies.
Above all things, we must remain invisible.
The time has come to begin the exclusion ceremony.
Friends are more important than anything else, agreed?
The friends here in this classroom right now are us.
We are us.
Those who dare to contradict our feelings are nothing but a disgrace.
As are those who want to stick out from our crowd.
The ones that refuse to fit in with us are a nuisance.
People like that, those who don't follow social cues, are evil.
Sumika Izumino was eaten by a bear because she was one of them.
It's only natural, after all.
People who are evil get killed.
We're here to decide who that next evil will be so we can exclude them.
Let's search evil!
Let's go.
Let's find out.
Let's filter.
Let's dig into that.
Let's go.
Let's dig into the usa.
Select. The moment has finally come. I'm going to eat that girl. Kureha, you're mine. Slurp.
Kureha, did you have fun with your friend again today? Aw, you really love her, don't you, sweetie?
I want you to know, as long as you don't forget love, you'll never, ever be alone.
Just remember that, okay? Right. If I don't forget about love, I won't really be alone.
That's correct. A storm and flood warning has just been issued for the greater metro area.
We're seeing violent rain and wind. Residents in the following districts have been advised to evacuate.
If this applies to you, evacuate immediately.
Oh no, I gotta protect the flower bed.
Ah.
You came out too.
You came out, too.
Aren't you cold?
I'm perfect, since you're here with me.
I, um, I just want to say thank you for being my friend, I mean.
Sure, and thanks for being mine, too.
I won't do it. I won't back down on love.
To live is simple. One must continually forget, back down, and cast away.
Those who cannot replace the old with the new will eventually perish.
Beasts like us never live in the past, after all.
The only thing that exists is the present, emotions we feel in the now.
The mood, the rhythm of this moment, that is everything.
The invisible ones think they're in control, but they can only decide how to run closed worlds.
Oh, Ginko. Lulu will never forget the wonderful day she met you.
Do you remember? That was when you found her love. You brought it to her.
So no matter what happens, Lulu won't ever give up on love.
It seems the time for judgment has come. Growl, growl.
Yes.
Is your love the real thing?
You bet it is.
This is a challenge from the Wall of Severance, Kureha Tsubaki.
If your love is true, go to the roof immediately.
The bears are waiting for you.
Give yourself over to the bears, and your love will be approved.
I'll never forgive the bears. I'll ruin them. Everyone.
Everyone.
I've been waiting for you, my dear Kureha.
Mitsuko? What are you doing here?
Getting ready to eat you, of course.
So I've got some information you might want to know.
I'm the one who ate your beloved Sumika Izumino.
Yes, it was me. I'm a big bad bear.
What are you talking about?
This is probably hard for you to believe, but it is the truth.
To be specific, I'm a bear who's just pretending to be human.
A bear pretending to be human?
You got it. Want to know who that bear I shot was?
Konomi Yurikawa.
Konomi? But I thought she was more-
What? My friend?
Well, I suppose technically she was.
She obeyed me at least, and that was pretty swell of her.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Whenever you're deciding to be friends with someone,
it's imperative to make sure the lucky girl is just a little bit inferior to you.
They're always so much easier to control that way.
You don't have to look so incredulous.
Okay, fine. If you need proof I'm telling the truth, I can give it to you.
Wait, those aren't Sumikas.
Uh-huh. I take it you finally believe me.
I'm telling you, that girl was a freak job.
I mean, there she was, literally being eaten alive.
And yet all she did was worry about you.
I'm sorry. Oh, Kureha.
I can't fix your love now, or your mother's flower bed.
And I promised I wouldn't back down, too.
I hope you can forgive me one day, Kureha.
I'm sorry. I'm so, so sorry.
Oh, come on. As if you have it in you to shoot me.
Yeah, that rage there in your eyes is the reason I love you.
In fact, it's really starting to get me off. It's so hot.
In your blood, I can sense it furiously boiling its way through your veins.
Your scent is amazing. I can hardly stand what I'm smelling off you.
Come on. Get angrier for me.
I'll never forgive the bears. I'll ruin them. I swear. Everyone!
I already said it once. You simply don't have it in you to kill me.
No way. This can't be happening.
Such bad angrier. You missed me again.
What a shock. You missed me again.
You keep missing me.
Don't worry. I have a plan to make everything better.
In place of the Sumikai 8, I'll love you!
I love you!
We want to eat that girl!
We want to eat her right this minute!
This court is now in session!
Let the Yuri trial begin!
Your Honor, we need Yuri approval, fast!
I want to save Koreha Tsubaki, Growl Growl!
You say you want to save Koreha Tsubaki? Well, that hardly makes sense!
Why? You two are bears!
Growl! We will still eat humans, I promise!
If we don't eat them, we can't protect Ginko's love!
Ah, so you're blatantly admitting your crime in a court of law then!
Damn it, I'm cool!
Objection!
Surely you realize for a bear eating humans is hardly a crime!
Sparkle! Sparkle!
Please rule quickly! We have to save her now!
I see. For that is sexy! Shabbatadoop!
Defendant bears, I ask you, do you want to be invisible?
Or would you rather eat humans?
We'll eat!
Bring on the humans! Growl! Growl!
Growl!
I am now ready to declare the verdict!
Yuri! Approved!
Growl! Growl! Growl!
Growl! Growl!
Yuri! Approved!
Growl! Growl! Growl! Growl! Growl! Growl!
I won't back down.
Where am I?
You won't back down on your love, Karei, huh? Growl! Growl!
Growl! Growl! We know the truth! Only love can change the world!
Love can change the world!
Love can change... the world?
Yes! Love!
Your love!
What is this? Their tongues feel rough, but... they're also warm and kind! I've felt this before! Beware!
Or... beware!
Spooch!
Now! You can do it!
I can do it!
Give it to me! A promised kiss!
I hit her! I think... I think I killed her! No! It can't be! A bear in human form? No!
What did you want to talk to me about? If it's the exclusion ceremony, I'm sorry, but no can do. You aren't allowed to participate because you can't be our friend until you take part in the invisible storm.
I don't want to. Growl! Growl! Growl! Growl!
So instead, we'll tell you something you want to know! How's that sound, Erika Oniyama?
What is it?
First, answer this question! Where do you think your missing friends are?
Missing friends? You mean like Kariusha?
They're right there.
I don't... What is this?
This is the place we buried Kariusha Akai. Well, the parts we didn't eat.
Are we the best?
You what?
Are you what?
Are you the best?
You what?
Are you saying that... that you ate her?
You ate my friend?
I don't understand.
Why tell me?
Growl!
Because guess what we're gonna do?
It's time to eat.
Slurp.